# KARISSA UKA

# COMPUTER SCIENCE STUDENT

#### CONTACT

+44 7399 636788

ukakarissa@gmail.com

https://github.com/karissa-uka

Birmingham, United Kingdom

#### SKILLS

- Microsoft Excel
- Team Collaboration
- Figma
- Python
- Java
- ReactJS
- Critical thinking
- Decision making
- Project Management
- Mobile Design and Development

# EDUCATION

# Rosedale Academy - Meadowlands Canadian School

Ontario Secondary School Diploma (OSSD)

- Business Leadership
- Advanced Functions
- Data Management
- Physics
- English
- Calculus

# **Aston University**

**BSc Computer Science** 

- Object Oriented Programming
- Introduction of Artificial Intelligence
- Internet Applications & Database Design
- Mathematics for Computing Professionals
- Data Structures and Algorithms in Java
- Software Engineering
- Professional and Social Aspects of Computing

# ACHIEVEMENTS

- Placement student of the year award 2022/2023
- Black Excellence Nominee
- Placement in focus award 2022/2023

#### PROFILE

An enthusiastic bilingual student who is currently in her final year of Computer Science (BSc Hons) at Aston University. Through this CITP accredited course and my placement I have gained valuable experience through projects and industry collaborations for a robust portfolio pre-graduation. I am reliable, trustworthy & work well under pressure.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Welcome Desk Assistant**

Aston Students' Union

September 2023-Current

- Warmly greet and assist visitors and providing information about the organization
- · Manage inquiries and provide administrative assistance
- Control facility access, verify identities, and act as a point of contact during emergencies

#### **Student Activities & Voice Assistant**

Aston Students' Union

July 2022 - June 2023

- Engaged in face to face customer service for SA and Voice.
- Provided day to day administrative support within the SA and Voice office.
- Played a key role in developing the use of the digital membership system for all Aston clubs and societies.
- Prepared reports and research documents.
- Liaised with commercial third parties and negotiated sponsorships for Voice and SA events.
- Explored new and innovative ways to bring in commercial revenue to directly support the official Aston clubs and societies.
- Ensured that equal opportunities, diversity and data protection policies were adhered to in all activities.

# **Agency Staff**

**Evolve Hospitality** 

December 2022 - June 2023

- Worked as a bartender, waitress, hostess, kiosk worker, chef's assistant and kitchen porter
- Travelled to across the country to offer hospitality services.

#### **Transcriptionist**

Rev.com

August 2021- September 2021

- Transcribed video and audio files for customers across the world
- Worked on transcribing and interpreting different size and quality projects for various range of customers
- Immediate crosschecks of all projects worked on under a strict time limit.

# **Waitress & Assistant Supervisor**

Grills in and Out

July 2016- August 2017

- Taking orders and serving customers while simultaneously addressing their concerns or complaints.
- Addressing operational challenges to ensure a cohesive and efficient restaurant environment.
- Handle administrative tasks, including inventory management, cash handling, and compliance with safety regulations.